{
    "subject": "resource/Fatty's_Chance_Acquaintance",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.981242299079895,
            "question": "Is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8491804003715515,
            "question": "Where is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106760382652283,
            "question": "Is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance from a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7806037068367004,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Fatty's Chance Acquaintance's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.747413158416748,
            "question": "Fatty's Chance Acquaintance's nationality is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7382586002349854,
            "question": "What is the citizenship of Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7376863956451416,
            "question": "Fatty's Chance Acquaintance originates from which location?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.714992880821228,
            "question": "What country is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.698306143283844,
            "question": "Where does Fatty's Chance Acquaintance hail from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6611174941062927,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Fatty's Chance Acquaintance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7156_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Fatty's Chance Acquaintance hail from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7156_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Fatty's Chance Acquaintance associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7156_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fatty's Chance Acquaintance originates from which location?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7156_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7156_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance,\" including its release as an American short comedy film. Specifically, it mentions that the film is \"1915 American short comedy\" and lists \"United States\" under the \"Country\" field in the document details. Therefore, the statement that \"Fatty's Chance Acquaintance is from United States\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}